<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The goal is to turn data into information, and information into insight. on Xiaoqin Zhang</title>
    <link>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The goal is to turn data into information, and information into insight. on Xiaoqin Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What Can You Tell from 3 Million Traffic Accident Records in US</title>
      <link>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>On average, there are 6 million car accidents in the U.S. every year. That&amp;rsquo;s roughly 16,438 per day. Of these crashes, 22,471 caused only property damage. Over 37,000 Americans die in automobile crashes per year. Where do the majority of accidents happen? How the weather affect the accident severity? Which cities have the most accident occurrences?
This project is to use EDA (Exploratory Data Analysis) and data visualization to analyze around 3 million traffic accident records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Used Car Market: When You Should Buy or Sell</title>
      <link>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the velvet and silk which surrounded him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamically, Accurately, Quickly, To See How Many Are Vaccinated</title>
      <link>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/post/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/post/project-5/</guid>
      <description>In the twinkling of an eye, all was ready to execute Coppenole’s idea. Bourgeois, scholars and law clerks all set to work. The little chapel situated opposite the marble table was selected for the scene of the grinning match. A pane broken in the pretty rose window above the door, left free a circle of stone through which it was agreed that the competitors should thrust their heads. In order to reach it, it was only necessary to mount upon a couple of hogsheads, which had been produced from I know not where, and perched one upon the other, after a fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Stole the Money? An Machine Learning Detective Interview</title>
      <link>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/post/project-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/post/project-6/</guid>
      <description>We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on the part of the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sentiment is Tangible, Because You Can Store It</title>
      <link>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Poor Gringoire! the din of all the great double petards of the Saint-Jean, the discharge of twenty arquebuses on supports, the detonation of that famous serpentine of the Tower of Billy, which, during the siege of Paris, on Sunday, the twenty-sixth of September, 1465, killed seven Burgundians at one blow, the explosion of all the powder stored at the gate of the Temple, would have rent his ears less rudely at that solemn and dramatic moment, than these few words, which fell from the lips of the usher, “His eminence, Monseigneur the Cardinal de Bourbon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaggle Competition: Titanic, Who Will Survive?</title>
      <link>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the velvet and silk which surrounded him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xqzhang-moji.github.io/ananke/contact/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to contact me through these social media platforms:
   Platform URL     Weibsite: https://VeteranD.com   LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com   GitHub: https://github.com    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
